<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.zeroconf_ioslave</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <name>Zeroconf Support</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">دعم التكوين الصفري</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Поддръжка на Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Suport de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Suport de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Podpora Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Zeroconf-understøttelse</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für ZeroConf</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Zeroconf Support</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Implementación de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Zeroconfi toetus</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Zeroconf euskarria</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Zeroconf-tuki</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de « Zeroconf »</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Compatibilidade con Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">ज़ीरोकॉन्फ़ समर्थन</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Zeroconf-támogatás</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Supporto de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Dukungan Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Supporto per Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Zeroconf 지원</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Zeroconf palaikymas</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning van Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Zeroconf-støtte</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Obsługa Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Suporte para Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte ao Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Suport pentru Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Поддержка протокола Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Podpora Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Podpora Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Stöd för Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Підтримка Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxZeroconf Supportxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Zeroconf 支持</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Zeroconf 支援</name>
  <summary>Browse local network services in Dolphin's Network page</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">تصفح خدمات الشبكة المحلية في صفحة الشبكة في دولفين</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Преглед на локалните услуги в страницата Мрежа на Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Navega pels serveis de xarxa local a la pàgina Xarxa del Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navega pels serveis de xarxa local a la pàgina Xarxa de Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Gennemse lokale netværkstjenester på Dolphins netværksside</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Durchsuchen von lokalen Netzwerkdiensten in der Netzwerkseite von Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Περιήγηση σε τοπικές υπηρεσίες δικτύου στη σελίδα δικτύου του Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Browse local network services in Dolphin's Network page</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Explorar los servicios de la red local en la página de Redes de Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Kohalike võrguteenuste sirvimine Dolphini võrgulehel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Arakatu tokiko sareko zerbitzuak Dolphinen sareko orrian</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Selaa paikallisverkkopalveluja Dolphinin verkkolehdellä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Parcourir les services des réseaux locaux sur la page « Réseau » de Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Examine servizos da rede local na páxina «Rede» de Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">डॉलफ़िन के नेटवर्क पृष्ठ में स्थानीय नेटवर्क सेवाओं का विचरण करें</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Helyi hálózati szolgáltatások böngészése a Dolphin Hálózat lapján</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Cerca o naviga in le pagina de servicios de rete de Dolphin </summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Telusuri layanan jaringan lokal di halaman Jaringan si Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Sfoglia i servizi della rete locale nella pagina della rete di Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">Dolphin의 네트워크 페이지에서 로컬 네트워크 서비스 탐색</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Naršyti Dolphin tinklo puslapyje vietinio tinklo tarnybas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Bladeren in lokale netwerkservices in de netwerkpagina van Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Bla gjennom lokale nettverks­tenester på nettverkssida i Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądaj usługi w sieci lokalnej na stronie sieci Dolphina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Navegue nos serviços da rede local com a página de Rede do Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Navegue pelos serviços da rede local com a página de Rede do Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Răsfoiește servicii de rețea locală în pagina Rețea din Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр служб локальной сети в разделе «Сеть» диспетчера файлов Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Prehliadať sieťové služby v stránke Dolphina Siete</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Brskaj po lokalnih omrežnih storitvah v Dolphinu na strani omrežja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bläddra i lokala nätverkstjänster på Dolphins nätverkssida</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Навігація службами локальної мережі на сторінці мереж Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBrowse local network services in Dolphin's Network pagexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">在 Dolphin 的网络页面浏览本地网络服务</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">在 Dolphin 的網路頁面瀏覽本機網路服務</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Adds an entry to Dolphin's Network page to show local services such as printers which advertise themselves with DNSSD (called Avahi or Bonjour by other projects).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يضيف مدخلاً إلى صفحة الشبكة في دولفين لعرض الخدمات المحلية مثل الطابعات التي تعلن عن نفسها باستخدام DNSSD (تسمى Avahi أو Bonjour بواسطة مشاريع أخرى).</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Добавя запис в Мрежа на Dolphin, за да покаже локалните услуги, като например принтери, които се декларират с DNSSD (наричани Avahi или Bonjour от други проекти).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Afegeix una entrada a la pàgina Xarxa del Dolphin per a mostrar els serveis locals com impressores que s'anuncien amb DNSSD (s'anomena Avahi o Bonjour en altres projectes).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afig una entrada a la pàgina Xarxa de Dolphin per a mostrar els serveis locals com impressores que s'anuncien amb DNSSD (s'anomena Avahi o Bonjour en altres projectes).</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Føjer en indgang til Dolphins netværksside til at vise lokale tjenester såsom printere der annoncerer sig selv med DNSSD (kaldes også Avahi eller Bonjour af andre projekter)</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Fügt der Seite Dolphin's Network einen Eintrag hinzu, um lokale Dienste wie Drucker anzuzeigen, die sich über DNSSD bekannt machen, bei anderen Projekten Avahi oder Bonjour genannt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Προσθέτει μια εγγραφή στη σελίδα του δικτύου του Dolphin για να εμφανίζει τοπικές υπηρεσίες όπως εκτυπωτές οι οποίοι αυτοαναγγέλλονται με το DNSSD (ονομάζεται Avahi ή Bonjour από άλλα έργα).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Adds an entry to Dolphin's Network page to show local services such as printers which advertise themselves with DNSSD (called Avahi or Bonjour by other projects).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Añade una entrada a la página de Redes de Dolphin para mostrar los servicios locales, como impresoras, que se anuncian a sí mismos mediante DNSSD (llamado Avahi o Bonjour en otros proyectos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Dolphini võrgulehele kirje lisamine, mis näitab kohalikke teenusi, näiteks printereid, mis teavitavad enda olemasolust DNSSD kaudu (mis teistes projektides kannab Avahi või Bonjouri nime).</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Tokiko zerbitzuak erakusteko sarrera bat gehitzen dio Dolphinen sareko orriari, DNSSD (beste proiektu batzuek Avahi edo Bonjour deitzen diete) erabiliz beraien burua aurkezten duten inprimagailuak esaterako.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Lisää Dolphinin verkkolehdelle tietueen, joka näyttää DNSSD:llä (joka muissa ohjelmissa tunnetaan myös nimillä Avahi ja Bonjour) itsensä ilmoittavat paikalliset palvelut kuten tulostimet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ajoute un menu dans la page « Réseau » de Dolphin permettant d'afficher les services locaux, par exemple les imprimantes, qui s'annoncent par l'intermédiaire de « DNSSD » (appelé « Avahi » ou « Bonjour » par d'autres projets).</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Engade unha entrada á páxina «Rede» de Dolphin para mostrar servizos locais como impresoras, que se anuncian mediante DNSSD (que outros proxectos chaman Avahi ou Bonjour).</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">डॉल्फ़िन के नेटवर्क पृष्ठ में स्थानीय सेवाएँ जैसे की प्रिंटर जो अपने आप को डीएनएसएसडी के साथ प्रचारित करते हैं (दूसरे परियोजनाओं मे अवाही या बॉनजूर कहलाता है) का प्रलेख जोड़ता है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Felveszi a Dolphinban a Hálózat alá azokat a helyi szolgáltatásokat, például nyomtatókat, amik DNSSD-n keresztül hirdetik magukat (máshol Avahi vagy Bonjour néven ismert).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Adde un entrata al pagina de rete de Dolphin per monstrar servicios local tal como imprimitores que annuncia se mesme con DNSSD(appellate Avahi o Bonjour per altere projectos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Menambahkan entri ke halaman Jaringan si Dolphin untuk menampilkan layanan lokal sepertihalnya printer yang mengiklankan dirinya sendiri dengan DNSSD (disebut Avahi atau Bonjour berdasarkan proyek lain)</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Aggiunge una voce alla pagina della rete di Dolphin che mostra i servizi locali come le stampanti che si auto-annunciano tramite DNSSD (chiamato Avahi o Bonjour da altri progetti).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Dolphin의 네트워크 페이지에 DNSSD(Avahi, Bonjour로도 알려져 있음)로 자기 자신을 알리는 프린터와 같은 로컬 서비스 항목을 추가합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Į programos Dolphin tinklo puslapį, prideda įrašą, skirtą rodyti vietines tarnybas, tokias kaip spausdintuvai, kurie skelbiasi naudodami DNSSD (kituose projektuose dar vadinamą kaip Avahi ar Bonjour)</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Voegt een item toe aan de netwerkpagina van Dolphin om lokale services te tonen zoals printers die zichzelf adverteren met DNSSD (Avahi of Bonjour genoemd door andere projecten).</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Legg til ei oppføring i nettverkssida i Dolphin for å visa lokale tenester, for eksempel skrivarar kunngjer seg sjølv via DNSSD (vert kalla Avahi eller Bonjour i nokre andre prosjekt).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dodaje wpis do strony sieci Dolphina, aby pokazać lokalne usługi takie jak drukarki oraz ogłosić się przez DNSSD (zwanym Avahi lub Bonjour w innych projektach).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Adiciona um elemento à página de Rede do Dolphin que mostra os serviços locais, como as impressoras que se anunciam a elas próprias com o DNSSD (chamado de Avahi ou Bonjour noutros projectos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Adiciona um item à página de Rede do Dolphin que mostra os serviços locais, como as impressoras que se auto-anunciam com o DNSSD (chamado de Avahi ou Bonjour por outros projetos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Adaugă o înregistrare la pagina Rețea din Dolphin ce arată servicii locale cum ar fi imprimante ce se anunță prin DNSSD (numit Avahi sau Bonjour în alte proiecte).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Поддержка протокола Zeroconf позволяет использовать страницу «Сеть» диспетчера файлов Dolphin для просмотра доступных в  локальной сети служб, использующих для аннонсирования различные реализации протокола DNSSD (Avahi, Bonjur и прочие).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Pridá položku na stránku siete v Dolphin, na zobrazenie miestnych služieb, ako sú tlačiarne, ktoré sa propagujú sami s DNSSD (nazývané Avahi alebo Bonjour podľa iných projektov).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Doda vnos na strani Dolphin's omrežje, da prikaže lokalne storitve, kot so tiskalniki, ki se oglašujejo z DNSSD (imenovani tudi Avahi ali Bonjour pri drugih projektih).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Lägger till en post på Dolphins nätverkssida för att visa lokala tjänster såsom skrivare, som tillkännager sig med DNSSD (kallat Avahi eller Bonjour av andra projekt).</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Додає на сторінку «Мережа» Dolphin пункт для показу служб локальної мережі, зокрема принтерів, які повідомляють про себе за допомогою DNSSD (системи, яка має назву Avahi або Bonjour у інших проєктах).</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAdds an entry to Dolphin's Network page to show local services such as printers which advertise themselves with DNSSD (called Avahi or Bonjour by other projects).xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">在 Dolphin 的网络页面添加新项，显示通过 DNSSD (在其他项目中叫做 Avahi 或 Bonjour) 广播的本地服务，比如打印机。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dolphin</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">network-workgroup</icon>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/zeroconf-ioslave/zeroconf-ioslave.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07"/>
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09"/>
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12"/>
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21"/>
  </releases>
</component>
