<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.zeroconf_ioslave</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <name>Zeroconf Support</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Suport de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für ZeroConf</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Υποστήριξη zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Zeroconf Support</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Implementación de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Zeroconf euskarria</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Supporto per Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Zeroconf 지원</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning van Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Obsługa Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Suporte para Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte ao Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Podpora Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Stöd för Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Підтримка Zeroconf</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxZeroconf Supportxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Zeroconf 支持</name>
  <summary>Browse local network services in Dolphin's Network page</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Navega pels serveis de xarxa local a la pàgina Xarxa del Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Durchsuchen von lokalen Netzwerkdiensten in der Netzwerkseite von Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Περιήγηση σε τοπικές υπηρεσίες δικτύου στη σελίδα δικτύου του Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Browse local network services in Dolphin's Network page</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Explorar los servicios de la red local en la página de Redes de Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Arakatu tokiko sareko zerbitzuak Dolphinen sareko orrian</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Parcourir les services des réseaux locaux sur la page Réseau de Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Sfoglia i servizi della rete locale nella pagina della rete di Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">Dolphin의 네트워크 페이지에서 로컬 네트워크 서비스 탐색</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Bladeren in lokale netwerkservices in de netwerkpagina van Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Przeglądaj usługi w sieci lokalnej na stronie sieci Dolphina</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Navegue nos serviços da rede local com a página de Rede do Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Navegue pelos serviços da rede local com a página de Rede do Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Prehliadať sieťové služby v stránke Dolphina Siete</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Bläddra i lokala nätverkstjänster på Dolphins nätverkssida</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Навігація службами локальної мережі на сторінці мереж Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBrowse local network services in Dolphin's Network pagexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">在 Dolphin 的网络页面浏览本地网络服务</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Adds an entry to Dolphin's Network page to show local services such as printers which advertise themselves with DNSSD (called Avahi or Bonjour by other projects).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Afegeix una entrada a la pàgina Xarxa del Dolphin per a mostrar els serveis locals com impressores que s'anuncien amb DNSSD (s'anomenen Avahi o Bonjour en altres projectes).</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Fügt der Seite Dolphin's Network einen Eintrag hinzu, um lokale Dienste wie Drucker anzuzeigen, die sich über DNSSD bekannt machen, bei anderen Projekten Avahi oder Bonjour genannt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Προσθέτει μια εγγραφή στη σελίδα του δικτύου του Dolphin για να εμφανίζει τοπικές υπηρεσίες όπως εκτυπωτές οι οποίοι αυτοαναγγέλλονται με το DNSSD (ονομάζεται Avahi ή Bonjour από άλλα έργα).</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Adds an entry to Dolphin's Network page to show local services such as printers which advertise themselves with DNSSD (called Avahi or Bonjour by other projects).</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Añade una entrada a la página de Redes de Dolphin para mostrar los servicios locales, como impresoras, que se anuncian a sí mismos mediante DNSSD (llamado Avahi o Bonjour en otros proyectos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Tokiko zerbitzuak erakusteko sarrera bat gehitzen dio Dolphinen sareko orriari, DNSSD (beste proiektu batzuek Avahi edo Bonjour deitzen diete) erabiliz beraien burua aurkezten duten inprimagailuak esaterako.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ajoute un menu dans la page Réseau de Dolphin permettant d'afficher les services locaux, par exemple les imprimantes, qui s'annoncent par l'intermédiaire de DNSSD (appelé Avahi ou Bonjour par d'autres projets).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Aggiunge una voce alla pagina della rete di Dolphin che mostra i servizi locali come le stampanti che si auto-annunciano tramite DNSSD (chiamato Avahi o Bonjour da altri progetti).</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Dolphin의 네트워크 페이지에 DNSSD(Avahi, Bonjour로도 알려져 있음)로 자기 자신을 알리는 프린터와 같은 로컬 서비스 항목을 추가합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Voegt een item toe aan de netwerkpagina van Dolphin om lokale services te tonen zoals printers die zichzelf adverteren met DNSSD (Avahi of Bonjour genoemd door andere projecten).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Dodaje wpis do strony sieci Dolphina, aby pokazać lokalne usługi takie jak drukarki oraz ogłosić się przez DNSSD (zwanym Avahi lub Bonjour w innych projektach).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Adiciona um elemento à página de Rede do Dolphin que mostra os serviços locais, como as impressoras que se anunciam a elas próprias com o DNSSD (chamado de Avahi ou Bonjour noutros projectos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Adiciona um item à página de Rede do Dolphin que mostra os serviços locais, como as impressoras que se auto-anunciam com o DNSSD (chamado de Avahi ou Bonjour por outros projetos).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Lägger till en post på Dolphins nätverkssida för att visa lokala tjänster såsom skrivare, som tillkännager sig med DNSSD (kallat Avahi eller Bonjour av andra projekt).</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Додає на сторінку «Мережа» Dolphin пункт для показу служб локальної мережі, зокрема принтерів, які повідомляють про себе за допомогою DNSSD (системи, яка має назву Avahi або Bonjour у інших проєктах).</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxAdds an entry to Dolphin's Network page to show local services such as printers which advertise themselves with DNSSD (called Avahi or Bonjour by other projects).xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">在 Dolphin 的网络页面添加新项，显示通过 DNSSD (在其他项目中叫做 Avahi 或 Bonjour) 广播的本地服务，比如打印机。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dolphin</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Network</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">network-workgroup</icon>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/zeroconf-ioslave/zeroconf-ioslave.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
